血族上集回顾
Previously on The Strain.
啊 儿子
Ah, mi hijo.
两个孩子都回家了 真好
So good to have my two kids together again.
要我跟你说多少次
How many times I have to tell you?
别把垃圾留在走道里
Don't leave your recycling in the hallway.
我们要谈谈你对我妈妈说话的态度
Now we're talking about the way you speak to my mother.
如果她再告诉我 你用这种态度跟她说话
If she ever tells me you talk to her like that again,
那别人就会在那些你最爱的垃圾桶里
they're gonna find your body
找到你的尸体
in one of those recycling bins you love so much.
棺材里面是什么 土壤
What was in that coffin? Soil...
那个橱柜去哪儿了
Where's that cabinet?
那箱子有500磅重
That box was 500 pounds;
不可能那样把它举起来的
nothing could lift it up like that.
棺材在你们手上 那么他也在你们手上
If you have the coffin, then you still have him!
别让他渡过河
Do not allow it across the river!
某种邪恶的东西在这里蔓延 老鼠一般是不会这么大批出洞的
Something evil has taken root. Rats don't migrate like that.
有东西在把他们赶出地底下
Something's driving them out from underground.
那东西深藏在底下黑暗处
It's hiding down there in the dark.
我搜了空荡鼠穴的中心地带
I tracked the epicenter of the rat-free zone.
我们要检查所有世贸中心附近
We have to look at all the decommissioned tunnels
的拆除了的隧道
near the World Trade Center.
消灭掉血祖 他的爪牙们也难逃一死
Kill the Master, and his spawn will die.
他们来了
They're coming.
额 好的
Uh... Alright.
紫外炸弹测试
UV light bomb test.
嘿 不不不 过来 来
Hey! No, no, no. Come on! Come on!
哈莱姆区 东118街
- 那我什么都看不到了 - 这就对了
- Now I can't see anything. - That's right.
总比让紫外射线
It's better than burning
烧伤你的视网膜要好
out your retinas looking at the UVC rays.
真不公平
No fair.
这真的是个好主意么
This is a... good idea?
好吧 我们正要看看是不是
Well, we're about to find out.
小心炸弹
Fire in the hole!
咱最好把火灭了
You might want to put that out.
- 什么情况 - 用工程术语讲 呃
- What happened? - In engineering terms, uh...
就是 测试失败了
you'd call that a fail.
史诗级的失败
An epic fail.
好吧 在持续的时间里 紫外光还是挺强的
Well, light was strong while it lasted.
- 持续时间足够得长来伤害到人吗 - 也许要更长
- Was it long enough to hurt them? - Could be bigger.
要让灯泡足够亮才行
Need to keep the bulbs bright enough to do the job
同时又不会过快地烧坏
without burning them out so fast.
如果是我
Well if it were me,
我会让灯泡周期性亮暗闪烁
I would make the lights cycle on and off,
就像照相机里的闪光灯
strobe like a camera flash.
这样灯泡就不会烧坏了
That might stop the bulbs from burning out.
我还装一台喷雾机 你懂的 再打点鼓
I could rig up a fog machine too, you know, crank some tunes,
这样我们就可以跳街舞了 就像 嘣 嘣 嘣
really get 'em dancing. Just boom, boom, boom.
那当我没说
Forget I mentioned it.
- 你还想不想 - 我在开玩笑啊 博士
- Do what you want. - I'm just joking, Doc.
我没说不同意 因为我确实赞成你的想法
I'm not saying I disagree because I do agree with you.
别从你的高头大马上掉下来
Don't fall off your high horse.
问题是 是
Problem is, is that...
视频字幕由 SSK字幕组 制作发布
字幕只供学习 请勿做任何商业行为
敬请关注新浪微博@SSK字幕组
好吧 我们没法再做测试了
well, we can't do any more tests.
我可以安上我剩下的灯泡
I could put the rest of our bulbs in...
翻译：香蕉奶昔 冬可可 Rubens Jophy     校对：Jophy
把电路板补好 装个振荡器
tinker with the circuit board, put in an oscillator...
但我们还得从这堆烂摊子开始
But we're gonna have to go with what we end up with.
- 希望没啥问题 - 费茨先生
- Hope for the best. - Mr. Fet,
压制：hhjie     时间轴：阿黎  络睿     总监：Jophy
你刚描述的那种方法
you've just described my method of operation
我过去用了60年
for the past six decades.
合作贴吧：百度《美剧血族》吧
百度《美剧血族》吧
血族
第一季  第十一集
妈妈 你在做什么
Mama, what are you doing?!
这该死的厨房里什么都找不到
I can't find anything in this damn kitchen!
显然她是在找她之前的那个
Apparently she's searching for an ashtray she once owned
从布宜诺斯艾利斯的阿拉维尔酒店里得到的烟灰缸
from the Alvear Hotel, Buenos Aires.
我知道就在这儿的什么地方
I know it's here somewhere.
妈妈
Mama...
那个多年前就坏了 嗯
that broke years ago. Hm?
我来收拾干净
I'll clean it up.
这儿不是你自己的厨房
This is not your kitchen.
这里有个烟灰缸
An ashtray here.
谢谢
Thank you.
我不喜欢他
I don't like him.
塞特拉基安先生是这里的主人
Mr. Setrakian is our host.
他的灵魂好黑暗
He has a dark soul.
妈妈 够了
Mama, basta.
妈妈够了 我们是客人
你这样不礼貌
对不起
I'm sorry.
我理解她所经历的一切
I understand what she's experiencing.
她做的不对 她关于你的说法也不对
She's wrong, what she said about you.
不 她是对的
No, she's not.
你妈妈还好吗
Is your mother going to be OK?
有时候她会犯糊涂
She gets confused sometimes.
她会混淆记忆和现实中的事儿
She mistakes memories for reality.
她一定很喜欢那个烟灰缸
She must have really liked that ashtray.
是一个酒店里弄到的
It was from a hotel-restaurant
我父亲第一次和她约会的地方
where my father took her on their first date.
他想要一个纪念品 因为他那个时候就知道
He wanted a memento, because he knew right then,
从第一个晚上开始就知道 他一定会娶她
from that first night, that he was gonna marry her.
这样的话 也许她记得这事儿 也是好的
Well then, maybe it's good that she still remembers it.
我想你是对的
I think you're right.
哈莱姆区 东115街
克里斯宾 开门
Crispin, open the door.
克里斯宾 该死的开门啊 我不是在玩 哥们儿
Crispin, open the damn door! I'm not playing, bro!
妈妈
Mama?
妈妈呢
Where's Mom?
克里斯宾 你听到了吗 妈妈在哪儿
Crispin, do you hear me? Where is Mom?
不
No!
不 不
No! No!
首先 别伤害到人
First, do no harm.
情况不一样了
Things have changed.
真的吗
Have they?
好比说一个遥远的村庄 比如200多年前的
Take a remote village, say 200 years ago.
村民们出现了奇怪的症状
Residents are manifesting strange symptoms.
死亡 恐惧 迷信 四处弥漫
Dying, fear and superstition rule the day,
人们说村子遭到了诅咒 直到有一天就像你和我一样的人出现了
and a curse is blamed until someone like you or me shows up
然后 通过一系列科学的方法
and, through a scientific process of elimination,
我们找到了瘟疫的源头 消灭了它
traces the disease to a source and destroys it.
诅咒解除 人民得救
The curse is lifted. People are saved.
秩序重建
Order is restored.
就是说你现在也相信了
So you believe now?
如果我们把血祖杀了 那么这场吸血鬼瘟疫
If we slay the Master, this plague of vampirism
- 就能结束 - 我只能相信
- ends today? - I have to believe it.
不然 我也不会把扎克留在这儿
Otherwise, I can't justify leaving Zach here
冒着成为孤儿的险
at the risk of
或是更糟糕
being orphaned or worse.
- 我们会成功会回来的 - 万一我们回不来呢
- We'll make it back here. - What if we don't?
也许我们中的一个要留下
Maybe one of us should stay.
你是说我
You mean me?
我绝不会要你留下
I would never ask you that.
你刚就说了
You just did.
- 我的答案是不 - 我不是那个意思
- The answer is no. - I didn't mean it like that.
我把我妈妈留着这里了
I'm leaving my mother behind.
我知道我知道
I know, I know you are.
我们俩不是刺客
You and I are not assassins.
费特 那个杀戮为乐的除害师
Fet, that kill-happy exterminator,
这个神风任务只是他的白日梦
this kamikaze mission is his wet dream.
那老头也被古老的仇恨所侵蚀
And the old man is consumed by an ancient grudge.
他们没有备用计划
They hace no plan B,
因为他们只能自己去冒这个险
because they have no one but themselves at risk.
我觉得我们别无选择
I don't think we have any other choice.
这是金 肯特特的武器
This was the weapon Jim Kent chose to use.
由你带着 是对他的致敬
You would honor him by taking it.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 你什么时候能回来 - 最晚到太阳落山
- When will you be back? - Sundown, absolute latest.
- 那就是一整天了 - 我会尽早的
- That's the whole day! - Hopefully sooner.
那妈妈怎么办
What about mom?
我觉得最好的办法就是
I think the best thing is to
除掉那个
take out that
引发了这一切的源头 塞特拉基安先生知道怎么做
the thing that's causing all this. Mr. Setrakian has a plan.
我知道 可为什么我不能一起去
I understand, but why can't I come with you?
我不知道那儿是什么情况
I don't know what's out there. I,
我不能控制那儿的情况 但是这里
I can't control that environment, but here,
你也看到塞特拉基安先生的地下室了
You've seen Mr. Setrakian's basement,
简直是个堡垒
it's a fortress,
是个军火库 最安全的地方
it's an armory. It's the most safe place
- 我能想象你在那儿很安全 - 你要小心 好吗
- I could imagine for you. - You'll be careful, right?
当然
Of course.
我保证 同时 你要看好马丁内斯夫人
I promise. In the meantime, keep an eye on Mrs. Martinez.
不应该是她来看好我么
Shouldn't that be the other way around?
也是
Should be.
但你是当家的 你要守在地下室里
But you're in charge. You stay in the basement.
你们俩都是 不要让任何人看到你们
Both of you. Don't let anybody see you.
好
Ok.
该走了
Time to go!
我知道你很勇敢
You're brave.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you too.
孩子 我的烟灰缸在哪
Young boy! Where is my ashtray?
不知道 这里没有
I don't know, it's not here.
你把它拿到哪去了
What did you do with it?
我没碰过 等诺拉回来了她会帮你找到的
I didn't put it anywhere. Nora can help when she comes back.
我女儿去哪了
Where is my daughter?
她和其他人一起出去了
She went out with all the others.
她把我的烟也拿走了吗 我要抽烟
Is she getting my cigarettes? I need my cigarettes.
你看 我要烟了
See? I need cigarettes!
你不能 我妈说过不能抽烟的
You shouldn't... My mom says you shouldn't smoke.
等诺拉回来了她会给你的
Nora will get you some when she comes back.
赶紧拿走 快点
Let's haul ass! Come on!
- 现在每个人都有的忙了 - 每个人都是自私自利的
- Everybody's having fun now. - Every man for himself.
这正是血祖所期望看到的
That's what the Master is counting on.
快跑 快跑
Run! Run! Run! Run!
快接电话啊 妈妈
C'mon, Mama, pick up.
求你了 快接电话
Pick up, mama, please.
欢迎致电
Thank you for calling
哈莱姆医疗中心
Harlem's Hospital Center.
如果您知道分机号码
If you know your party's extension...
麻烦请瓜达卢佩 埃利萨尔德接电话
Yeah, can I speak to Guadalupe Elizalde, please?
我有急事
It's an emergency.
请问你是
May I ask who's calling?
我是奥古斯丁 埃利萨尔德 她的儿子
It's Augustine Elizalde, her son.
好的 请稍等
Yeah, hold on.
嗯
Ok.
奥古斯丁 埃利萨尔德女士的班是到六点
Mr. Elizalde, Guadalupe's shift is until 6 pm.
现在这里一片混乱
It's totally crazy here.
她之前也许有来过 我不清楚
She might have called in early or come here early, I don't know.
不过我没看见她
But I haven't seen her.
好吧 谢谢了
OK. Thank you.
来人啊 救救我
Somebody please! Help me!
我要出去
I need to get out of here!
救命
Help!
我被关在里面了 快帮帮我
It's locked! Help me, please!
帮帮我
Help me!
求求你们了
Please.
马丁内斯夫人
Mrs. Martinez!
你终于来了 孩子
Oh, there you are, young boy.
钥匙 快把钥匙给我
The keys! Give me the keys.
爸爸把钥匙给我了 你要到里面楼下去吗
My dad gave me the keys. Do you want to go back downstairs?
我女儿 我的诺拉
My daughter, my Nora,
他们把她带走了 我必须去找她
they've taken her. I must go to her!
不是的 她是自己跟他们一起走的 她会回来的
No, she left on her own. She's coming back.
- 他们都会回来的 - 他们不会回来的 不会
- They're all coming back! - They never come back! Never!
我们必须离开这里
We must leave this place!
求你了
Please!
- 我要离开这里地方 - 如果
- I need to get out of here! - If I...
如果我去给你找些香烟来
If I go get you cigarettes,
你能在楼下安静地等我吗
will you go downstairs and wait for me?
为什么是世贸中心
Why the World Trade Center?
血祖经常出没于人类悲惨的地方
The Master is drawn to places of great human misery.
曼哈顿 钱伯斯街车站
他被痛苦所吸引
He seeks out suffering.
食尸鬼的味道
Eau de strigoi.
我想我们来对地方了
I think we're in the right place.
不入虎穴
"The cave you fear to enter...
焉得虎子
Holds the treasure that you seek."
噢 上帝啊
Oh, God!
马丁内斯医生 运气好的话
With any luck, Dr. Martinez,
前面还会遇到比这更糟的地狱
it's gonna get a hell of a lot messier than this.
都往右边靠
Stay to the right!
第三轨道
The third rail.
不知道是不是在这下面 不过
I don't know if it's live down here, but, uh...
这可有625伏电压 最好别碰
that's 625 volts; we don't want to find out.
这些东西都代表了他们每个人的一生
It's everything that defined these people.
我可不想
Well, I hope I'm defined
让钱包和一块手表来总结我的人生
by more than just my wallet and my wristwatch.
你看到的每一样东西都象征着别人的母亲
Everything you see represents somebody's mother,
- 父亲 儿子 女儿 - 不用跟他纠结了
- father, son, daughter. - Don't bother.
跟着一辆灰色的福特或普利茅斯
Following either a gray Ford or a Plymouth...
正在追捕两个逃亡南方的白种男性
We're looking at two male Caucasians moving south...
你的手机还能用吗 有信号吗
Does your phone work? Can you get a signal?
没有 我的手机也用不了
No, mine doesn't work either.
没有痕迹了
No more graffiti.
911事件后这个地方就被遗弃了
The station was abandoned after 9/11...
之后恐怕就没人来过这里了
Doubt anyone's been here since.
当然我指的是活生生的人
Anyone still human that is.
他们群居在这里
They're nesting.
通常都是在白天的时候
During daylight hours, always.
尤其是第一次变异
Especially when first turned.
变异的过程会消耗他们很多精力
The, uh, transformation, it exhausts them.
这么多脖子够我们砍的了
That's a lot of necks to chop.
不
No.
先放着不管
Releasing them...
不然血祖会注意到我们的存在 都关掉
would alert the Master to our presence. Switch off.
凯利
Kelly?
不是她 伊弗
Eph, it's not her.
我们得继续前进
We must keep moving.
要是我当时在场保护你就好了 妈妈
I should have been there for you, Mama.
法雷尔先生
Mr. Farrell...
你是来收房租的对吧
you're here for the rent, puto?
看 这里的轨道很干净
Look. The rails are clean here.
嗯 给车留的
Ah, service cars.
他们用这些废弃的车站来调转方向
They use the abandoned stations for turnarounds.
我对这些地下通道可是了如指掌 这条线
I know these tunnels like the back of my hand. Now, this line
是建在1923年的一条老线之上的
was built on top of the old original 1923 line.
它就像
Yeah, it's like, uh...
古罗马或者是耶路撒冷
ancient Rome or the City of David.
我们听过很多次这种声响了 博士
We were hearing that the whole time, Doc.
不 不一样
No, no, this is different.
这些隧道 它们发出一些奇怪的声响
These tunnels, they do strange things to sounds.
就像 就像一个窃窃私语的小厅
You know, like whispering chambers.
知道吗
You know?
如果有火车来了 我们会知道的
If there's a train coming, we're gonna know it, OK?
快来
Come on.
-跑 -快跑
- Go! - Run!
你刚说啥来着
You were saying?
我对这些隧道了如指掌
"I know these tunnels like the back of my hand."
怕你不知道 这是你的手背
For future reference, that's the back of your hand.
那是你的屁股 你的手肘
That's your ass. That's your elbow.
你想带路么
You want to take lead, yeah?
带吧
Take point? Then go ahead.
随便吧 带路吧 博士
Be my guest. Go for it, Doc.
我受够这个自大的家伙了
I'm sick of this Brooklyn-pride shit.
你还是省省吧
Save it for somebody who cares.
你是非要强辩到底了啊
You're used to having the last word, huh, Doc?
一个当铺老板或者买鼠药的人比你都知道的多
How does it feel to know that a pawnbroker
这种感觉怎么样
and a rat killer know more than you do, huh?
你为此等了一辈子了 是么
You've been waiting for this your whole life, haven't you?
恭喜你 你的吸血鬼末日要到来了
Congratulations on the vampire apocalypse.
开始即灭亡
The first will be last.
灭亡即新生 博士
The last shall be first, Doc.
够了 你们俩 注意点
Enough! Both of you! Pay attention!
我们不能被发现了
We cannot afford to be seen.
还不行
Not yet.
真是挑的一条好路走 一群蠢货
It's a shitty way to go, even for them.
好吧 又发现一个新方法杀死他们了
Now, I know another way to kill them.
下次出来 你带上变压器
Next outing, you carry the power transformer.
她朝这个方向走 我们应该很近了
She was heading this way, so we're close.
小心点
Just be careful.
他们会更好一点 大规模的抢劫活动
...or, they'll get any better. Widespread looting.
-紧急救援已经展开 -有人吗
- Emergency services stretched. - Hello?
公共基础设施被破坏 专家人士预测
Infrastructure's crumbling, and there are serious concerns
未来可能还会发生供水系统的瘫痪和损坏
that hydro and water services are in imminent danger of collapse.
此外 昨晚发来的报道
Added to that, last night's events,
在乔治华盛顿大桥上
on the George Washington's bridge particularly,
最近一次警戒部署引发人民的关注
has sparked concerns over a recent wave of vigilantism
从而引发大规模的恐慌
that has spread panic over law-abiding citizens.
许多市民决定
And many citizens have actually
举家迁徙 搬离这个城镇
decided to pull up stakes and get out of town.
我们现在正连线一位准备搬家的市民
We have one such gentleman on the line right now...
噢 中头奖了
Ohhh, jackpot!
这里真是乱糟糟的
Sloppy seconds is more like it.
食物就是食物
But food's food.
检查一下收银箱
Check the cash register just in case.
多装几袋食物 我们可以把吃不完的用来交换别的东西
And grab another bag to fill. We'll trade what we can't eat.
这样的商店我们怕是找不到第二家了
We might not find another store like this again.
噢 该死
Ohhh... Damn!
嘿 维尔 这个收银员 他
Hey, Val, the clerk, he, uh...
别像个胆小鬼一样
Don't be such a pussy.
你不想要食物了么
You want to eat, don't you?
看看储藏室 找点罐装金枪鱼
Check the backroom, look for canned tuna.
-噢 天呐 -放开我
- Oh, Jesus! Hey! - Let go of me!
你在这儿干吗 小鬼 嘿 瓦珥
What are you doing here, kid? Hey, Val!
你从哪儿来 小鬼
Where did you come from, kid?
还有人在这儿
Somebody else here.
嘿 小心点儿 小鬼
Hey, watch it, kid.
快走
Vamoose.
-死路 -搞什么鬼
- Dead-end. - What the hell?
那些吸血鬼都去哪儿了
Where did all the vamps go? Where'd they...
他们怎么通过的
How'd they get through?
如果我是在捉老鼠的话
If I were hunting rats,
那么这里一定是他们去的地方了
this is exactly where I'd assume they'd go.
或者 这是个陷阱
Or if this is a trap.
该死
Goddamn it!
这边没问题
All clear.
该死 他们跟着我们
Shit. Behind us.
走
Go.
快走 我拖住他们
Hurry. I'll hold them off.
他知道我们在这里了
He knows we're here now.
好吧 那还不快点
Oh well, all the more reason to hurry.
伊弗
Eph?
博士
Doctor!
伊弗 你在吗
Eph, are you there?
搭把手
Give me a hand.
古德温泽博士
Dr. Goodweather!
我好冷
I'm so cold.
来找我 伊弗 我需要你
Find me, Eph, I need you.
-凯莉 -别过去
- Kelly? - Don't!
-听我说 -别让他们伤害我
- Listen to me! - Don't let them hurt me.
博士
Doctor!
不
No!
听我说
Listen to me!
-博士 -那边有事发生了
- Doctor! - Something's happening.
光用光拖着他们不能解决问题
Holding them off with the light isn't gonna get it done.
走 快走
Go! Go now!
走
Go!
伊弗
Eph!
Eph?
他们在哪
Where are they?
我们走
Let's go.
伊弗
Eph?
伊弗 你在哪 快
Eph, where are you? Hurry.
凯莉 我在这
Kelly, I'm here.
她在哪里 该死的 来啊
Where is she? Goddamn it, come on!
你们在等什么 来啊
What are you waiting for?! Come on!
你是来毁灭我的吗
Have you come here to destroy me?
那个老教授
The old professor...
有个了新学生
has a new pupil...
来送死 像他当年那样
...to fail... as he failed.
我夺走了他所有的一切
I have taken everything from him.
而我
And I...
也会夺走
will take everything...
你的一切
from you.
你的妻子
Your wife...
你的儿子
your son.
我
I...
是人类的吞噬者
am a drinker of men.
教授
Professore.
马丁斯尼夫人
Mrs. Martinez!
Mrs. Martinez?
马丁斯尼夫人
我给你拿了香烟
I got your cigarettes.
哦 谢谢
Oh, thank you!
可爱的小男孩
Sweet young boy.
有人看见了吗 他往哪个方向跑的
Did anyone see? Which way did he go?
哪条路
Which path?
-我们找到他了 -不 是他找到了我们
- We had him. - No, he had us.
你没事吧
Are you OK?
我没事
I think so.
-你看见他了 -是的 我看见他了
- You saw him? - Yeah, I saw him.
我听到了她的声音
I heard her voice.
凯莉
Kelly.
她朝着我大喊
She was calling out to me.
-他戏弄了我 -当然 他戏弄了你
- He tricked me. - Of course, he tricked you!
你怎么能那样跑掉
How could you run off like that?
我们差点就要猎捕你而不是猎捕那东西了
We ended up hunting for you instead of that thing!
你为什么要点燃光弹 那东西把他都驱跑了
Why did you ignite the light bomb? It chased him away!
-我们没得选 -他就在那里
- We had no choice! - He was right there!
就在我咫尺之遥 现在他都跑了
Right within my grasp! Now gone!
除非毁了血祖 否则我不会停下来的
I'll not rest until the Master is destroyed!
事到如今 他也不会停下来的
And now, neither will he!
我砸了你  你
I'll break you, you...
食尸鬼
strigoi!
杀了你 去死 你去死
Kill you! Die, you!
去死 食尸鬼
Die, strigoi!
走这边
This way!
你怎么知道他往这边去
How did you know he went this way?
血祖就在这附近
The Master is here somewhere.
我们得找出他在哪里 重新布阵
We should think this out, regroup.
然后再让他们重新布阵 为什么要那样做
And let them regroup? Why would we do that?
我们可能再也不会有这样的机会了
We may never get this chance again.
-该死 -艰难的选择哈
- God damn it! - Tough choice here, huh?
这只是个基本的随机选择
That's basically a random choice.
不是
No.
听着 我想到了
Look... I get it,
虽然我和你是同一阵线的 但这很疯狂
I'm on your side, but this is crazy.
我们让他落荒而逃
We've got him on the run!
要乘胜追击 做好你的本分
We must press on! Do what you like!
-住手 -先等一下
- Stop! - Hold on!
关掉手电筒
Flashlights off.
只开紫外线灯
UV only.
看到了吗
You see?
我说的没错 现在 我先走
I was right! Now, let me go!
停下来 等等 诺拉
Stop! Wait. Nora.
我们还等什么
What are we waiting for?
那边有很多怪物
That's a lot of monsters.
不能过去 老头
No way, Pops!
他就在这 别拉我
He is here! Unhand me!
看在上帝的份上 你这是在自杀
For God's sake, this is suicide!
不 不 不 不
No! No! No! No!
新浪微博@SSK字幕组·合作贴吧《美剧血族》吧
更多精彩内容敬请关注新浪微博@SSK字幕组
如果你对这部剧有什么看法请进入百度贴吧《美剧血族》吧